https://www.lightech.co.uk/company/privacy

Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 83
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 85
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 87
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 89
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 91
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 95
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 109
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 115
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 124
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 131
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 137
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 137
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 149
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 156
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 163
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 169
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 175
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 181
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 188
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 195
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 203
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 211
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 224
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 229
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 234
Deprecated:
Function ereg_replace() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 242
Deprecated:
Function ereg_replace() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 244
Deprecated:
Function eregi() is deprecated in /var/sites/l/lightech.co.uk/public_html/scripts/browser.php on line 247
What we need
Lightech Sound and Light Ltd will be what is known as the 'Controller' of the personal data you provide to us. Lightech's company registration number is 4517675 and its registered address is Bramhall Hill Farm, Bank Lane, North Rode, Congleton, Cheshire, CW12 2PJ.
Unless otherwise agreed with you, we will only collect basic personal data about you, which does not include any special categories of personal information about you (often known as ‘sensitive personal data’). This information does, however, include the likes of your name, address, telephone number and email address.
Why we need it
We need to know basic personal data in order to provide you with the services you have engaged us to provide, and to assert out right to be recompensed in return for those services, as per the service agreement or contract we have with you. If you do not provide this information then we may be unable to provide the services you have requested. We will not collect any personal data from you that we do not need in order to provide the services we have agreed to provide you with.
What we do with it
All the personal data we hold about you will be processed by our staff in the United Kingdom and no third parties will have access to your personal data unless there is a legal obligation for us to provide them with this. We take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal data is processed securely and more information on this can be requested.
How long we keep it
We will generally keep your personal data for a minimum of 6 years, if you consent to marketing, any information we use for this purpose will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. Further information on our retention schedule can be requested.
What we would like to do with it
We would like to send you information about our own products and services by post, telephone and email. Please note that if you consent to being sent our marketing information we will not share your information with any third-party companies.
Call 01260 223666
Email info@lightech.co.uk
Home
Services
Wedding Lighting
Marquee Lighting
Venue Lighting
Party & Special Effects Lighting
Lightech Sound and Light Ltd.
Bramhall Hill Farm,
North Rode,
Congleton,
Cheshire,
©2020 Lightech Sound & Light Ltd.
